[
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The Romans had   *insatiable*  appetites for everything. ",
        "answers": [
            "huge",
            " impatient",
            "sudden",
            "intermittent"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "huge"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Congress was   *hesitant*  to repeal the Prohibition Act. ",
        "answers": [
            "willing",
            " urged",
            "reluctant",
            "supposed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "reluctant"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "  *Deceptively*  simple in design, the sculptural works of Isamu  Noguchi incorporate a broad range of textures, sizes, and contours. ",
        "answers": [
            "Misleadingly",
            " Generally",
            "Noticeably",
            "Exceptionally"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Misleadingly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Under  the major's able  *leadership* , the soldiers found safety. ",
        "answers": [
            " guidance",
            "intensity",
            "flagship",
            "ability"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " guidance"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  Chinese people worship their  *ancestors* . ",
        "answers": [
            " fossils",
            "elders",
            "forefathers",
            "heirs"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "forefathers"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Phosphorus is used in paints  for highway signs and markers because it is  *bright*  at night.  ",
        "answers": [
            " luminous",
            "harmless",
            "adequate",
            "attractive"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " luminous"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Thomas Edison's office  was always  *disorganized*  with books and papers. ",
        "answers": [
            "cluttered",
            " decorated",
            "sorted",
            "stacked"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "cluttered"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "One of the responsibilities  of a forest ranger is to  *drive slowly*  through the area in search  of animals in distress. ",
        "answers": [
            "cruise",
            "race",
            "skid",
            "swerve"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "cruise"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Even though the evidence is overwhelming, if one juror  is still  *skeptical* , the case must be retried. ",
        "answers": [
            "not  present",
            "not surprised",
            "not convinced",
            "not worried"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "not convinced"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " A human body requires more nutrients in cold weather because more energy is  necessary to  *maintain*  body temperature. ",
        "answers": [
            " surpass",
            "preserve",
            "equip",
            "reach"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "preserve"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "There are hundreds of  *species*  of eels, some  living in fresh water but most living in oceanic waters. ",
        "answers": [
            " specialties",
            "relatives",
            "kinds",
            " offspring"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "kinds"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Fainting, or a temporary loss of consciousness, may be brought  about by an  *insufficient*  supply of oxygen to the brain. ",
        "answers": [
            " inappropriate",
            "inadequate",
            "unstable",
            " undiluted"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " inappropriate"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Many   *properties*  of the atmosphere affect the amount of solar radiation  that reaches the earth. ",
        "answers": [
            "belongings",
            "impurities",
            "levels",
            " characteristics"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " characteristics"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  Sahara, the world's largest desert,  *extends*  over 9 million square  kilometers. ",
        "answers": [
            "spreads",
            "sits",
            "presents",
            "condenses"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "spreads"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The   *most secure*  type of bolt is a deadbolt. ",
        "answers": [
            " heaviest",
            "most costly",
            "most common",
            "safest"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "safest"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When Joan of Arc described  her vision, her voice did not  *hesitate* . ",
        "answers": [
            "amplify",
            " falter",
            "dissolve",
            "mumble"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " falter"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  earliest canoes were made from  *hollowed*  tree trunks. ",
        "answers": [
            " sturdy",
            "burnt",
            "heavy",
            "emptied"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "emptied"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "It is  much easier to talk about social change than it is to  *make it  happen* . ",
        "answers": [
            "acknowledge it",
            "predict it",
            "bring it  about",
            "put up with it"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "bring it  about"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "That he should ask her  to marry him was rather  *presumptuous*  on his part. ",
        "answers": [
            " audacious",
            "stupid",
            "brave",
            "nice"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " audacious"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The judge's decision was  made  *impartially*  since he knew both parties personally. ",
        "answers": [
            "quickly",
            "without  prejudice",
            "immediately",
            "clearly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "without  prejudice"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In the 1960's the upper level of Pennsylvania Station in  New York City was  *torn down*  and replaced by Madison Square Garden.  ",
        "answers": [
            " detracted",
            "demoted",
            "distended",
            "dismantled"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "dismantled"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "American children   *customarily*  go trick-or-treating on Halloween. ",
        "answers": [
            " gaily",
            "traditionally",
            "readily",
            "inevitably"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "traditionally"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "According to scientists, it  is possible that another Ice Age will  *soon*  be upon us. ",
        "answers": [
            "some  day",
            "now",
            "in the near future",
            " undoubtedly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "in the near future"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " *Efficiency*  was lacking in the  company's management, and consequently productivity suffered. ",
        "answers": [
            " Effectiveness",
            "Diligence",
            "Honesty",
            " Cooperation"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " Effectiveness"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Nearly half of the town's inhabitants are descendants of   *indigenous*  civilizations. ",
        "answers": [
            " native",
            "backward",
            "hard-working",
            "poor"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " native"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Though many scientific breakthroughs have  resulted from  *mishaps* , it has taken brilliant thinkers to  recognize their potential. ",
        "answers": [
            "misunderstandings",
            "accidents",
            " misfortunes",
            "incidentals"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "accidents"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "During the Great  Depression, there were many  *wanderers*  who traveled on the  railroads and camped along the tracks. ",
        "answers": [
            "vagabonds",
            " tyros",
            "zealots",
            "veterans"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "vagabonds"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "We decided to pay for the furniture on the   *installment*  plan. ",
        "answers": [
            "cash and carry",
            "piece by  piece",
            "monthly payment",
            "credit card"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "monthly payment"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Mail service will be   *suspended*  during the postal workers' strike. ",
        "answers": [
            "inspected",
            " delayed",
            "uninterrupted",
            "curtailed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "curtailed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "  *Domestic*  cats in the United States are generally classified in ten  short-haired breeds and seven long-haired breeds. ",
        "answers": [
            " Household",
            "Friendly",
            "Trained",
            "Foreign"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " Household"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Translating literally from one language to another  *works*   unsatisfactorily at best. ",
        "answers": [
            "pays",
            "functions",
            "reads",
            " labors"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "functions"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " General acceptance of 3-D films may prove hard to  *come by* , as the  experience of three decades ago indicated. ",
        "answers": [
            " obtain",
            "explain",
            "understand",
            "discern"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " obtain"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  gorilla, the largest of the apes, is now able to be bred in   *confinement* . ",
        "answers": [
            "haste",
            "safety",
            "captivity",
            " intervals"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "captivity"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Every year, each  households in the United States discards approximately a ton of   *trash* . ",
        "answers": [
            "filler",
            "garbage",
            "paper",
            "fuel"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "garbage"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The accident occurred because the truck driver was   *careless* . ",
        "answers": [
            "alert",
            "negligent",
            "subsequent",
            " decrepit"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "negligent"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Honeybees live in a  *complicated*  society of ten to fifty thousand  members. ",
        "answers": [
            "concealed",
            "complex",
            "cooperative",
            "congested"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "complex"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When Benjamin Franklin became the first American postmaster  general in 1775, he worked to improve the frequency and   *reliability*  of mail delivery. ",
        "answers": [
            " satisfaction",
            "opportunity",
            " dependability",
            "extent"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " dependability"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When he won the first prize  he realised that this was the highest  *attainment*  of his life.  ",
        "answers": [
            " accomplishment",
            "task",
            "surprise",
            "shock"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " accomplishment"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Recent studies have shown  that the  *statute*  of male Americans has scarcely in the past two  hundred years. ",
        "answers": [
            "weight",
            "height",
            "life span",
            "head size"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "height"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Travel agents will  *confirm*  your  reservations for you free. ",
        "answers": [
            "purchase",
            "verify",
            "exchange",
            " obtain"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "verify"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Marcia's career involved a  *dual*  role for her as a counselor and a  teacher. ",
        "answers": [
            "tiring",
            "dedicated",
            "twofold",
            " satisfying"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "twofold"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " The  *blank space*  of the paper must be 1.5 inches at the top and 1  inch at the bottom and on the sides. ",
        "answers": [
            " frames",
            "borders",
            "shutters",
            "margins"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "margins"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Early log cabins were   *crude*  if sturdy structures. ",
        "answers": [
            " unpainted",
            "resilient",
            "unseasoned",
            "rough"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "rough"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When the protestor entered the meeting clad only in a  beach towel, the audience was  *dumbfounded* . ",
        "answers": [
            " speechless",
            "excited",
            "content",
            " applauding"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " speechless"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The walnut is a deciduous tree that   *bears*  valuable nuts. ",
        "answers": [
            "enriches",
            "yields",
            "replaces",
            "hides"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "yields"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In the early days of baseball, the game was  played by young men  *of means*  and social position. ",
        "answers": [
            "with  skill",
            "with equipment",
            "with money",
            "with ambition"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "with money"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Alexander Hamilton remained  *adamantly*   opposed to the policies of John Adams throughout the latter's presidency. ",
        "answers": [
            "admirably",
            " strongly",
            "inflexibly",
            "manfully"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "inflexibly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Did  you remember to fill the  *thermos* ? ",
        "answers": [
            "jug",
            " flask",
            "tank",
            "battery"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " flask"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Marcia and Bill were the  *recipients*  of the president's scholarship  for fine arts. ",
        "answers": [
            "creators",
            "donors",
            "receivers",
            "instigators"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "receivers"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The news of the president's death   *astonished*  the world. ",
        "answers": [
            " alerted",
            "admonished",
            "atoned",
            "astounded"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "astounded"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Ethnocentrism prevents us from  *putting up  with*  all of the customs we encounter in another culture. ",
        "answers": [
            "experiencing",
            " adopting",
            "comprehending",
            "tolerating"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "tolerating"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " The tetracyclines are a family of antibiotics used to  *infection* .  ",
        "answers": [
            " battles",
            "contamination",
            "injury",
            "deterioration"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "contamination"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " There are many  *potential*  dangers ahead of the inexperienced scuba  diver. ",
        "answers": [
            "exciting",
            "novel",
            "horrid",
            "possible"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "horrid"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "One should always  *temper*  enthusiasm with  caution. ",
        "answers": [
            "modify",
            "compare",
            "replace",
            "encourage"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "modify"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When Professor Baker  suffered a  *return of his illness* , he was ordered to enter the  hospital. ",
        "answers": [
            "rebuff",
            "reform",
            "relapse",
            "resort"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "relapse"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "They had always thought  the volcano  *inactive* . ",
        "answers": [
            "interesting",
            " dangerous",
            "silent",
            "extinct"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "silent"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " When preparing a  *diet* , a person should be aware that vitamin D  acts to increase the amount of calcium absorbed by the body. ",
        "answers": [
            "schedule of  exercises",
            "nutritional plan",
            "study on longevity",
            "medicinal chart"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "medicinal chart"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "If you  don't get the  *gist*  of this article ask the teacher in the morning.  ",
        "answers": [
            " idea",
            "conclusion",
            "detail",
            "copy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " idea"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A good auditorium will assure that the sound is   *able to be heard* . ",
        "answers": [
            "superior",
            "genuine",
            " audible",
            "contained"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " audible"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Reagan seemed   *sure*  that he would win the election. ",
        "answers": [
            "eager",
            " hopeful",
            "confident",
            "resigned"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "confident"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Library cards will   *expire*  when they are not used. ",
        "answers": [
            "cost more  money",
            "cease to be effective",
            "be mailed to the holder",
            "be continued  automatically"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "cease to be effective"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Collections of opals and  quartz are featured at the City Museum's annual exhibition of  *precious  stones* . ",
        "answers": [
            "coins",
            "loot",
            "gems",
            "shells"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "gems"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " *Lifting the shoulders*  is a gesture that  indicates lack of interest. ",
        "answers": [
            "Napping",
            "Shrugging",
            " Sighing",
            "Yawning"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Shrugging"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The American bald  eagle is not really  *bald*  in the usual sense. ",
        "answers": [
            "mighty",
            " majestic",
            "hairless",
            "flightless"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "hairless"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Poet Emma  Lazarus is perhaps best known for having written the sonnet inscribes on the   *pedestal*  of the Statue of Liberty. ",
        "answers": [
            "inside",
            " base",
            "torch",
            "replica"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " base"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Primary education in the United States is   *compulsory* . ",
        "answers": [
            "free of charge",
            "required",
            "excellent",
            " easy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "required"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "  *Mounting*  evidence indicates that acid rain is damaging historic  sites in Boston and Philadelphia. ",
        "answers": [
            "Hanging",
            "Tentative",
            " Increasing",
            "Irrefutable"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " Increasing"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Jan took many  *snapshots*  while on vacation in  Europe. ",
        "answers": [
            "notes",
            "gifts",
            "photos",
            "clothes"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "photos"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Double agents live in a  *perpetual*  state of fear. ",
        "answers": [
            " perfect",
            "constant",
            "ceasing",
            "perpetrated"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "constant"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Neon is an element which  does not combine readily with any other element; because of this property, it is  called an  *inactive*  element. ",
        "answers": [
            "inert",
            " adjacent",
            "explicit",
            "obsolete"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "inert"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Canada  and the United States are cooperating to clean up the  *dirty*  lakes  along their borders. ",
        "answers": [
            "contaminated",
            "huge",
            "mutual",
            "gorgeous"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "contaminated"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When Pope John Paul  visited Latin America, he often  *signaled for*  children to come to  him. ",
        "answers": [
            "denied",
            "adored",
            "beckoned",
            " allowed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "beckoned"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "  *Interfering*  with someone's mail is a serious crime in the United  States. ",
        "answers": [
            "Assisting",
            "Tampering",
            "Gambling",
            " Intimidating"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Tampering"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  development of general anesthetics has allowed doctors to operate without the   *pain*  once associated with surgery. ",
        "answers": [
            " fear",
            "protest",
            "rage",
            "anguish"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " fear"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Cowrie shells were once in widespread use as  *a  token*  of value. ",
        "answers": [
            "a symbol",
            "an amount",
            "a thing",
            "an  investment"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a symbol"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Our final assignment  for the English class is to give an  *impromptu*  speech. ",
        "answers": [
            " eloquent",
            "unprepared",
            "technical",
            "unbiased"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "unprepared"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Techniques that create an atmosphere of suspense are commonly used by filmmakers  to  *arouse*  their audiences. ",
        "answers": [
            "excite",
            " harass",
            "appease",
            "arrest"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "excite"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Despite the  breakthrough, expectations remain  *modest* . ",
        "answers": [
            " thorough",
            "slight",
            "intricate",
            "shy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "slight"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Marvin's doctor said he was  *obese*  and had to  take immediate measures to correct the problem. ",
        "answers": [
            " anemia",
            "tired",
            "corpulent",
            "petulant"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "corpulent"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The meat must be  *chopped*  before it can be  used in that recipe. ",
        "answers": [
            "stewed",
            "bought",
            "cut",
            " cooked"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "cut"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Silver was  *eliminated from*  quarters with the Coinage Act of 1965.  ",
        "answers": [
            "reduced  from",
            "added to",
            "removed from",
            "increased in"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "removed from"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The   *remnants*  of the Roman Empire can be found in many countries in  Asia, Europe, and Africa. ",
        "answers": [
            "effects",
            "small pieces",
            "buildings",
            " destruction"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "small pieces"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "John Dewey  *loathed*  the idea that  children should not participate in activities as part of their educational  experience. ",
        "answers": [
            "encouraged",
            "noticed",
            "hated",
            " began"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "hated"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "It takes  *roughly*  4000 pounds of petals to make  a single pound of rose oil. ",
        "answers": [
            "as much as",
            "amazingly",
            "more or  less",
            "relatively"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "more or  less"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Macrame is used to make clothing and accessories as  well as  *ornamental*  items. ",
        "answers": [
            " colorful",
            "decorative",
            "utilitarian",
            "hand-made"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "decorative"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "He could   *barely*  stand up after completing the marathon, even though he won.  ",
        "answers": [
            " hardly",
            "still",
            "really",
            "bravely"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " hardly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In the past, energy sources were thought to be   *boundless* . ",
        "answers": [
            "without limits",
            "inexpensive",
            "natural",
            " solar"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "without limits"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "It is  better to try to change things than to  *complain*  about them. ",
        "answers": [
            "ramble",
            " straddle",
            "grumble",
            "dangle"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "grumble"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Joyce is loved by all her friends because  she is very  *congenial* . ",
        "answers": [
            " pleasant",
            "wealthy",
            "courageous",
            "sensitive"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " pleasant"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "There are   *considerably*  more weekly newspapers than daily newspapers in the  United States. ",
        "answers": [
            "mostly",
            "hardly",
            "rarely",
            " substantially"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " substantially"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " *Proximity to*  the court house  makes an office building more valuable. ",
        "answers": [
            "Interest in",
            "Similarity  to",
            "Nearness to",
            "Usefulness for"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Nearness to"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "It is obvious that Mary Anne  *greatly  loves*  her new husband. ",
        "answers": [
            "adores",
            "admires",
            " affects",
            "abhors"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "adores"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "With a new project the   *initial*  stages are often the key to success. ",
        "answers": [
            "final",
            " first",
            "concluding",
            "preparatory"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " first"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Modern techniques have  made  *dentures*  virtually unnoticeable. ",
        "answers": [
            "false  teeth",
            "surgical implants",
            "artificial hair",
            "plastic  surgery"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "false  teeth"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Mark  cannot talk well because he has a speech  *impediment* . ",
        "answers": [
            " skeptic",
            "defect",
            "imposition",
            "aspect"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "defect"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " The raccoon is a  *nocturnal*  animal. ",
        "answers": [
            " harmless",
            "night",
            "marsupial",
            "diurnal"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "night"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "  *Variations*  in the color of sea water from blue to green seem to be  caused by high or low concentrations of salt. ",
        "answers": [
            " Changes",
            "Descriptions",
            "Measures",
            "Clarity"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " Changes"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  calf of the human leg  *contains*  seven muscles. ",
        "answers": [
            " includes",
            "requires",
            "makes use of",
            "depends on"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " includes"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The   *daring*  young man rode through the Indian village trying to find  his long-lost sister. ",
        "answers": [
            "bold",
            "cowardly",
            "persistent",
            " captured"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "bold"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The new  manager's  *aggressive*  behavior soon turned all the employees  against him. ",
        "answers": [
            "shy",
            "depressed",
            "hostile",
            " unstable"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "hostile"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "He was  *refused*  admission to the  restaurant for not wearing a tie. ",
        "answers": [
            "granted",
            "denied",
            " acquiesced",
            "appealed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "denied"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The revolutionary  forces had to  *muster up*  enough men to oppose the British Army.  ",
        "answers": [
            " finance",
            "disguise",
            "convince",
            "gather"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "gather"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "We  watched as the plane  *disappeared*  behind the clouds. ",
        "answers": [
            " melted",
            "escaped",
            "vanished",
            "perished"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "vanished"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "It is difficult to get young people to plan for their old  age, which seems very  *distant*  to them. ",
        "answers": [
            " impossible",
            "faraway",
            "observable",
            " fearful"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "faraway"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A few   *spots*  of paint splattered on the floor in spite of the care that  we took to cover it. ",
        "answers": [
            "speaks",
            "tricks",
            "cracks",
            "bricks"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "speaks"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  passengers on the boat were  *mesmerized*  by the motion of the sea.  ",
        "answers": [
            " paralysed",
            "hypnotized",
            "nauseated",
            "reverberated"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "hypnotized"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In  some countries, nuclear power  *produces*  up to two-thirds of the  necessary electricity. ",
        "answers": [
            "makes",
            "receives",
            "dissipates",
            " manages"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "makes"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Defined most   *broadly* , folklore includes all the customs, beliefs, and  traditions that people have handed down from the generation to generation.  ",
        "answers": [
            " fancifully",
            "liberally",
            "quaintly",
            " dryly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " dryly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  campers heard a strange  *rustling*  in the trees. ",
        "answers": [
            " stealing",
            "pillaging",
            "movement",
            "fight"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "movement"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The company asked for  *additional*   information. ",
        "answers": [
            "certain",
            "emphatic",
            "further",
            " enchanting"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "further"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " It is no  *simple*  matter for chimpanzees accustomed to living with  human beings to return to the wild. ",
        "answers": [
            "foolish",
            " easy",
            "common",
            "unique"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " easy"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Computerized  editing systems are the  *norm*  in major newsrooms today. ",
        "answers": [
            " rule",
            "requirement",
            "value",
            "specialty"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " rule"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A  series of  *calamities*  can severely affect underwriters' earnings.  ",
        "answers": [
            " reports",
            "investments",
            "becalmings",
            "disasters"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "disasters"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Speech difficulties may  sometimes be  *overcome*  if a person is shown where to place the  tongue and teeth to make sounds. ",
        "answers": [
            "identified",
            "minimized",
            " surmised",
            "surmounted"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "surmounted"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Legislators are considering whether the drug laws for  possession of marijuana are too  *severe* . ",
        "answers": [
            "vague",
            " harsh",
            "diverse",
            "covert"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " harsh"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When snow   *collects*  on top of a building during the winter, the weight  sometimes weakens the construction, and occasionally causes the roof to  collapse. ",
        "answers": [
            "accumulates",
            "promulgates",
            " disseminates",
            "confiscates"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "accumulates"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "City taxes are  based on an  *estimate of the value*  of one's property. ",
        "answers": [
            " appraisal",
            "forecast",
            "diagnosis",
            "outline"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "forecast"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Since Ron has such an  *intense dislike*   for flying, I am certain that he will not want to go with us. ",
        "answers": [
            "avarice for",
            "aversion  to",
            "affection for",
            "affirmation of"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "aversion  to"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The flowers on the table were a  *manifestation*   of the child's love for his mother. ",
        "answers": [
            "a  demonstration",
            "an infestation",
            "a  combination",
            "a satisfaction"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a  demonstration"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The most  important environmental influence on fish is water temperature for fish tend to   *take on*  the temperature of their surroundings. ",
        "answers": [
            "assume",
            " regulate",
            "avoid",
            "exceed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "assume"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Neutron stars are incredibly dense stars that are formed  after the  *explosion*  of a supernova. ",
        "answers": [
            " brilliance",
            "dynamism",
            "expansion",
            " burst"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " burst"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "It is  possible for a chemist to use the melting point of a particular   *substance*  to determine its purity. ",
        "answers": [
            " liquid",
            "element",
            "quantity",
            "mixture"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "element"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " He is person who understands his  *obligations*  and attends to them.  ",
        "answers": [
            " restrictions",
            "annoyances",
            "observations",
            " duties"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " duties"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Contractors hire surveyors to mark the  *limits*  of the property  before they begin construction. ",
        "answers": [
            "basements",
            "expenses",
            " boundaries",
            "supplies"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " boundaries"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Many desert animals have made adaptations that are   *strikingly*  similar to those of desert plants. ",
        "answers": [
            " predominantly",
            "precipitously",
            "forcefully",
            " remarkably"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " remarkably"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Roget's  Thesaurus, a collection of English words and phrases, was originally arranged by  the ideas they express  *rather than*  by alphabetical order. ",
        "answers": [
            "restricted",
            "as well  as",
            "unless",
            "instead of"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "instead of"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A  feeling of sadness  *permeated*  the atmosphere. ",
        "answers": [
            " quieted",
            "pervaded",
            "stilled",
            "stifled"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "pervaded"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The president's  *compassion*  for the refugees  caused him to admit a very large number of them. ",
        "answers": [
            " friendship",
            "respect",
            "pity",
            " hostility"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "pity"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The Supreme Court has a reputation for being   *just* . ",
        "answers": [
            "stubborn",
            "impartial",
            "humorous",
            " capricious"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "impartial"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Practitioners of behavioral medicine   *encourage*  patients to be responsible for their own health. ",
        "answers": [
            " urge",
            "enlighten",
            "allow",
            "admonish"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " urge"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I was   *horrified*  to see the child about to cross the expressway alone.  ",
        "answers": [
            " ashamed",
            "shocked",
            "nervous",
            "surprised"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "shocked"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  museum dismissed the  *curator*  after some of the oldest paintings  were damaged. ",
        "answers": [
            "artist",
            "cleaner",
            "guard",
            "director"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "director"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Frontier settlements had to   *depend on*  the cavalry. ",
        "answers": [
            "visit",
            " trust",
            "meet",
            "help"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " trust"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " The plane took off and after a few seconds was barely  *visible* .  ",
        "answers": [
            " forgotten",
            "heard",
            "gone",
            "observable"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "observable"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The Boy Scouts usually sell  *apple  juice*  in the fall in order to earn money for their activities. ",
        "answers": [
            "punch",
            " ale",
            "cider",
            "soda"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "cider"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "He was  *mystified*   by the look on the stranger's face. ",
        "answers": [
            "perplexed",
            " shocked",
            "upset",
            "excited"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "perplexed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Relaxation therapy teaches one not to  *fret  over*  small problems. ",
        "answers": [
            "worry about",
            "get angry about",
            "get involved  in",
            "look for"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "worry about"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In Benjamin Franklin's almanac, he warns  against making  *hasty*  decisions. ",
        "answers": [
            " expensive",
            "unhealthy",
            "firm",
            "quick"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "quick"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Feudal society depended on the existence of  *faithful*  vassals.  ",
        "answers": [
            " diligent",
            "gullible",
            "pious",
            "loyal"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "loyal"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Crop irrigation has long played a role in  agricultural  *practices* . ",
        "answers": [
            " possibilities",
            "routines",
            "rehearsals",
            " services"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "routines"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Before  the earthquake hit the area,many minor  *tremors*  were felt. ",
        "answers": [
            " spasms",
            "noises",
            "vibrations",
            "crumblings"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "vibrations"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Mark Anthony's   *eulogy*  of Caesar at his funeral is memorably recorded in a play by  Shakespeare. ",
        "answers": [
            "prayer",
            "biography",
            "praise",
            " denunciation"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "praise"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The Morrill Act of 1862   *authorized*  the states to use federal lands for the establishment  of colleges that would offer programs in agriculture and the mechanical arts.  ",
        "answers": [
            " challenged",
            "persuaded",
            "empowered",
            "invited"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "empowered"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Most eyeglasses will not  *break into many  pieces*  because they are made with either plastic or a special blend of  glass. ",
        "answers": [
            "shatter",
            "tear",
            "collapse",
            "rupture"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "shatter"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The new  representative from our state is such an  *extrovert*  I think he'll  have problems. ",
        "answers": [
            "ambitious person",
            "out going person",
            "egoist",
            " underdog"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "out going person"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The Civil War in 1863   *cut*  the United States into two nations - a southern Confederacy  and a northern Union. ",
        "answers": [
            "severed",
            "acknowledged",
            "integrated",
            " alienated"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "severed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "George Washington's  armies set up  *an encampment*  at Morristown, New Jersey, for two  winters during the American Revolution. ",
        "answers": [
            "an  encounter",
            "a bivouac",
            "an encroachment",
            "a detainment"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a bivouac"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In the early 1960's many Southern   *communities*  were slow to desegregate their public schools. ",
        "answers": [
            " establishments",
            "communes",
            "states",
            " neighborhoods"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " neighborhoods"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " *Fragments*  of the Dead Sea Scrolls  have been found in recent years. ",
        "answers": [
            "aromas",
            "pieces",
            " drawings",
            "writers"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "pieces"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The National Institute of  Mental Health is conducting  *far-reaching * research to determine the  psychological effects of using drugs. ",
        "answers": [
            "extensive",
            " prevalent",
            "refined",
            "tentative"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "extensive"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The choir  sang as a  *preliminary event*  to the ceremony. ",
        "answers": [
            " precaution",
            "prelude",
            "precept",
            " precise"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "prelude"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " After the drops were placed in the patient's eyes, his pupils became   *dilated* . ",
        "answers": [
            "enlarged",
            "smaller",
            "irritated",
            " sensible"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "enlarged"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "An appendectomy is a   *routine*  operation. ",
        "answers": [
            "cheap",
            "small",
            "usual",
            "quick"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "usual"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Since the research studies  have shown a relationship between cancer and cigarette smoking, many people have   *cut down* . ",
        "answers": [
            "ceased smoking",
            "become frightened",
            "decreased the number of  cigarettes",
            "gotten sick"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "decreased the number of  cigarettes"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The General Motors Corporation is the   *principal*  industry in Pontiac, Michigan. ",
        "answers": [
            " chief",
            "oldest",
            "earliest",
            "automotive"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " chief"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "  *Carpets*  from countries such as Persia and Afghanistan often fetch  high prices in the United States. ",
        "answers": [
            "Artifacts",
            "Rugs",
            " Pottery",
            "Textiles"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Rugs"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Many weak  and  *incompetent*  rulers were overthrown by more powerful forces.  ",
        "answers": [
            " incapable",
            "impulsive",
            "clever",
            "greedy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " incapable"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The copperhead, a snake that strikes without warning,  is considered more  *dangerous*  than the rattlesnake. ",
        "answers": [
            " exquisite",
            "sporadic",
            "treacherous",
            "aloof"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "treacherous"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "For  your safety and the safety of others, always  *pay attention to*   traffic signals. ",
        "answers": [
            "overlook",
            "heed",
            "glance at",
            "repair"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "heed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A balance of international payment refers to the net  result of the business which a nation  *carries on*  with other  nations in a given period. ",
        "answers": [
            "cancels",
            "appropriates",
            "transacts",
            " mediates"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "transacts"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The new suit he has bought  is unfortunately made of  *synthetic*  material. ",
        "answers": [
            "blended",
            " silken",
            "artificial",
            "natural"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "artificial"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Taillevent's fame as a  *chef*  has endured since the 14th century.  ",
        "answers": [
            " cook",
            "soldier",
            "diplomat",
            "leader"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " cook"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Athlets learn to   *conceal*  their disappointment when they lose. ",
        "answers": [
            "ignore",
            " regret",
            "accept",
            "disguise"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "disguise"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "\"Uncle  Tom's Cabin\" has been frequently translated and often dramatized, most recently  as a  *curiously*  sentimental melodrama. ",
        "answers": [
            "an overly",
            "an  unfortunately",
            "an unambiguously",
            "an oddly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "an oddly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "They couldn't believe their  eyes looking at the  *contortionist* . ",
        "answers": [
            " exhibitionist",
            "painting",
            "acrobat",
            "fight"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "acrobat"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " *Unorganized*  guessing will not raise a test  score as significantly as choosing one letter as a \"guess answer\" for the entire  examination. ",
        "answers": [
            "Cryptic",
            "Haphazard",
            "Economical",
            " Subsequent"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Haphazard"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The   *recycling*  of aluminum converses ninety-percent of the energy  needed to make new metal. ",
        "answers": [
            "cleaning",
            "reprocessing",
            "reselling",
            " crushing"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "reprocessing"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A   *hot land covered with a dense growth of trees*  offers the best  climate for growing orchids. ",
        "answers": [
            "plateau",
            "plain",
            "jungle",
            "forest"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "jungle"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "We were caught in  a  *deluge*  while returning from our vacation. ",
        "answers": [
            " hailstorm",
            "downpour",
            "sandstorm",
            "blizzard"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "downpour"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The coroner was able to extract a  *minute*   particle of cloth from under the victim's fingernail. ",
        "answers": [
            " infinitesimal",
            "significant",
            "large",
            " short"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " infinitesimal"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In  the 1776 pamphlet \"Common Sense,\" Thomas Paine  *defended*  the cause  of the American Revolution. ",
        "answers": [
            "fought",
            "championed",
            " exposed",
            "believed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "championed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Astronomy provides the knowledge necessary for   *correct*  timekeeping, navigation, surveying and mapmaking. ",
        "answers": [
            "meticulous",
            " incessant",
            "accurate",
            "ancient"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "accurate"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Since you don't know them very  well, it would be  *suitable*  for you to send a card instead of a  gift. ",
        "answers": [
            "obstinate",
            "intricate",
            "appropriate",
            " ultimate"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "appropriate"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "  *Efficient*  air service has been made available through modern  technology. ",
        "answers": [
            "affluent",
            "modern",
            "inexpensive",
            "effective"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "effective"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " One of the most common uses of boric acid is as  *an antiseptic* .  ",
        "answers": [
            "a  solvent",
            "a bacteria",
            "a compound",
            "a  disinfectant"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a  disinfectant"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Many  doctors are still general practitioners, but the  *tendency*  is  toward specialization in medicine. ",
        "answers": [
            "rumor",
            "trend",
            "prejudice",
            " security"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "trend"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " If the teams were not so evenly matched, it would be easier to   *foretell*  the outcome of the Superbowl. ",
        "answers": [
            " argue",
            "predict",
            "discuss",
            "influence"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "predict"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " When he was director of the company, his first  *accomplishment*  was  to bring about better working conditions. ",
        "answers": [
            " accumulation",
            "achievement",
            "defeat",
            " job"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "achievement"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A credit union can  *distribute*  earnings to  its members as dividends. ",
        "answers": [
            "increase",
            "allocate",
            "implement",
            " augment"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "allocate"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "While  they were away on vacation, they allowed their mail to  *accumulate*   at the post office. ",
        "answers": [
            "be delivered",
            "pile up",
            "get lost",
            "be  returned"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "pile up"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "It is very  discourteous to  *intrude*  during someone's conversation. ",
        "answers": [
            "find fault",
            " disagree",
            "be in the way",
            "leave quickly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "be in the way"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The teacher decided to take  the students for a weekend  *trek* . ",
        "answers": [
            "visit",
            "study  tour",
            "seminar",
            "hike"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "hike"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The \"Mona  Lisa\" is the portrait of a woman with a very  *enticing*  smile.  ",
        "answers": [
            " oblivious",
            "luminous",
            "alluring",
            "elusive"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "alluring"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Chemicals are used to  *retard*  the growth of ornamental trees.  ",
        "answers": [
            " initiate",
            "stunt",
            "benefit",
            "alter"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "stunt"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I always  thought  *ornithology*  was for older people not for teenagers. ",
        "answers": [
            " rock-climbing",
            "the study of birds",
            "deep-sea  diving",
            "free-fall parachuting"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "the study of birds"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Rain   *lessens*  in the fall throughout most of the Appalachian Mountain  region. ",
        "answers": [
            "pours",
            "accumulates",
            "abates",
            " evaporates"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "abates"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  harp, with up to 47 strings, produces the most  *tones*  of any  stringed instrument. ",
        "answers": [
            "noise",
            "melodies",
            "sounds",
            " scales"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "sounds"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The test site region  *encompassed*  a  ten-square-mile area. ",
        "answers": [
            "overlooked",
            "owned",
            "surveyed",
            "encircled"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "encircled"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Although a cheetah can  *achieve*  a speed of 110  kilometers per hour, it can maintain this speed for only a few hundred meters.  ",
        "answers": [
            "race  at",
            "bypass",
            "uphold",
            "attain"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "attain"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The professor  reprimanded the  *tardy*  student. ",
        "answers": [
            "unpunctual",
            " sleepy",
            "impolite",
            "tiresome"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "unpunctual"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The secretary  left after weeks of  *harassment*  by the manager of her department.  ",
        "answers": [
            " teasing",
            "irritation",
            "absence",
            "goading"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "irritation"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When one is  unfamiliar with the customs, it is easy to make a  *blunder* . ",
        "answers": [
            "a commitment",
            "a  mistake",
            "an enemy",
            "an injury"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a  mistake"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Embroidery   *depicting*  scenic views became popular in the United States toward  the end of the eighteenth century. ",
        "answers": [
            "distorting",
            " commemorating",
            "portraying",
            "emphasizing"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "portraying"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Caffeine is a stimulant that was  *originally*  produced from plants  but now can be made under laboratory conditions. ",
        "answers": [
            " first",
            "appropriately",
            "often",
            "only"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " first"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The   *rooms and meals*  at the Campus Motel were not only adequate but  also inexpensive. ",
        "answers": [
            "registrations",
            "reservations",
            " accommodations",
            "confirmations"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " accommodations"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The new   *amphitheater*  was based on the ancient Greek design. ",
        "answers": [
            "underwater  theater",
            "oval theater",
            "sound and light theater",
            " mini-theater"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "oval theater"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " After a long, hard struggle, we  *gradually*  succeeded in having  people accept the truth of our theory. ",
        "answers": [
            " slowly",
            "momentarily",
            "suddenly",
            "graciously"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " slowly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The world's  *busiest*  airport is Chicago's  O'Hare, where each year 550,000 flights land and take off. ",
        "answers": [
            "best  run",
            "most active",
            "most spacious",
            "most  successful"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "most active"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The disinterred mummy was found to be in an advanced stage  of  *disintegration* . ",
        "answers": [
            "glorification",
            "saturation",
            " decomposition",
            "preservation"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " decomposition"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "People living along the  coast  *escaped*  inland before the hurricane hit. ",
        "answers": [
            "fled",
            " floundered",
            "flipped",
            "flattered"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "fled"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A   *multitude*  of people attended the fund-raising presentation in the  mall. ",
        "answers": [
            "small number",
            "select group",
            "huge crowd",
            "large  herd"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "huge crowd"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  *coveted*  Oscar was won by the best  performing actor. ",
        "answers": [
            "much desired",
            "rewarding",
            " outstanding",
            "highly regarded"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "much desired"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  *drought*   was finally over as the fall brought in some welcome rain. ",
        "answers": [
            "summer",
            " aridity",
            "heatwave",
            "harvest"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " aridity"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Drink  only  *tepid*  liquids. ",
        "answers": [
            "slightly warm",
            "very hot",
            "slightly cool",
            "very  cold"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "slightly warm"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The dog  saw his  *reflection*  in the pool of water. ",
        "answers": [
            " image",
            "bone",
            "imagination",
            "leash"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " image"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "After  *eating an excessive  amount*  at the dinner, he became ill. ",
        "answers": [
            " surfeiting",
            "lamenting",
            "exploiting",
            " inhabiting"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " surfeiting"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  *degree*  to  which heat affects tennis players' performance depends in part on the level of  humidity. ",
        "answers": [
            "extent",
            "temperature",
            "height",
            " strength"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "extent"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " *Prior  to*  his appointment as secretary of state, Henry Kissinger was a  professor of government and international affairs at Harvard. ",
        "answers": [
            "After",
            " Before",
            "During",
            "Instead of"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " Before"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "After Senator Smith announced that he  planned to run for president, the telephone at campaign headquarters rang   *continuously* . ",
        "answers": [
            "incessantly",
            "ignorantly",
            "incisively",
            " impartially"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "incessantly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "If a  student has a  *grievance*  she can always take it up with her  adviser. ",
        "answers": [
            "protest",
            "task",
            "difficulty",
            "sickness"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "protest"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A  *vacant*  apartment in New York City is  very difficult to find. ",
        "answers": [
            "good",
            "large",
            "empty",
            "clean"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "empty"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A satire by Mark Twain,  the story is about a prince and a  *very poor person*  who exchange  places for a time. ",
        "answers": [
            "pauper",
            "tyro",
            "recluse",
            "captive"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "pauper"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The students were given   *complimentary*  passes for the new movie. ",
        "answers": [
            " inexpensive",
            "free",
            "expensive",
            " good"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "free"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Exchange rates  for most  *currencies*  do not float freely. ",
        "answers": [
            " newspapers",
            "securities",
            "money",
            " finances"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "money"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Although buses are   *scheduled*  to depart at a certain hour, they are often late. ",
        "answers": [
            "listed",
            " requested",
            "obligated",
            "loaded"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "listed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In  certain types of poisoning, immediately give large quantities of soapy or salty  water in order to  *induce*  vomiting. ",
        "answers": [
            "control",
            " clean",
            "cause",
            "stop"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "cause"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "This tapestry has a very   *complicated*  pattern. ",
        "answers": [
            "appropriate",
            "obsolete",
            "ultimate",
            "intricate"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "intricate"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Tiny  Tim, a character in \"A Christmas Carol\" was a happy little boy in spite of the  disability that caused him to  *favor one leg* . ",
        "answers": [
            "limp",
            " weep",
            "rest",
            "shout"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "limp"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Insects are the most  *diverse*  class of animals in number, form, and  natural range. ",
        "answers": [
            "poetic",
            "intricate",
            "varied",
            "hard  working"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "varied"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  audience  *applauded*  enthusiastically after the performance at the  Grand Old Opera. ",
        "answers": [
            "clapped",
            "chatted",
            "laughed",
            " contributed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "clapped"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A series  of  *columns*  supporting a large porch is typical of the architecture  of pre-Civil War mansions in the South. ",
        "answers": [
            "statues",
            " murals",
            "pillars",
            "arches"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "pillars"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The child was rushed to  hospital after he  *ingested*  more than a dozen sharp nails. ",
        "answers": [
            "sat on",
            "fell  on",
            "swallowed",
            "stepped on"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "swallowed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Jane suffered a   *light blow*  on her head as she got out of the car. ",
        "answers": [
            "jump",
            " hump",
            "bump",
            "stump"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "bump"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "He was fired because of  his  *misconduct*  at the office party. ",
        "answers": [
            "mistake",
            " impropriety",
            "condition",
            "singing"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " impropriety"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The 1908 Siberian  meteorite explosion  *brought about*  considerable depletion of the  northern hemisphere's ozone layer. ",
        "answers": [
            "was caused by",
            "resulted  in",
            "brought back",
            "was initiated by"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "resulted  in"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The representatives of the company seemed very   *callous*  concerning the conditions of the workers. ",
        "answers": [
            "liberal",
            " ignorant",
            "responsible",
            "insensitive"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "insensitive"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Lindbergh's first  nonstop flight across the Atlantic Ocean was  *an act*  of great  daring and courage. ",
        "answers": [
            "a narrative",
            "a feat",
            "an attempt",
            "a conspiracy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a feat"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Her only chance to  elude her  *pursuer*  was to mingle with the crowd. ",
        "answers": [
            "friend",
            " lawyer",
            "follower",
            "captor"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "follower"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Scott  *seized*  the opportunity to present  his proposal to the director. ",
        "answers": [
            "realized",
            "grasped",
            " rendered",
            "delivered"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "grasped"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Pets sometimes   *imitate*  their owners, but seldom the other way round. ",
        "answers": [
            "follow",
            " copy",
            "annoy",
            "admire"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " copy"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "We will need to  *leave out*  some of the  preliminary exercises at the graduation because of the large number of students  receiving degrees. ",
        "answers": [
            "outfit",
            "omit",
            "audit",
            "quit"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "omit"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "People who live in the country enjoy a  *rustic*   life style. ",
        "answers": [
            "slow",
            "difficult",
            "simple",
            " happy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "simple"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Some scientists have argued that the purpose of the human  appendix may have been to digest uncooked meat and bark, functions that are   *no longer useful* . ",
        "answers": [
            "simulated",
            "perilous",
            " obsolete",
            "sluggish"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " obsolete"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The diver's task  was complicated by the fact that,  *besides*  the gold, the wreck  contained bombs and ammunition. ",
        "answers": [
            "next to",
            "away from",
            "allied  to",
            "in addition to"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "in addition to"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "He  decided to subscribe to the magazine although it only came out   *biannually*  ",
        "answers": [
            "biennial",
            "semi-annual",
            "four times a  year",
            "every year"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "semi-annual"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Only  five hundred people live in this tiny  *village* . ",
        "answers": [
            " hamlet",
            "metropolis",
            "ranch",
            "suburb"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " hamlet"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Most  of the  *wounded*  passengers were quickly removed from the aircraft.  ",
        "answers": [
            " unconscious",
            "injured",
            "deceased",
            " distressed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "injured"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " The  *plainer*  a bower bird's plumage, the more brightly it decorates  its nest to attract a mate. ",
        "answers": [
            "more spectacular",
            "duller",
            " flatter",
            "more melancholy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "duller"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Some of the gangs that  terrorized Chicago in the 1920s did not have the  *propriety*  to keep  their activities off the streets. ",
        "answers": [
            "decency",
            "ability",
            "resources",
            "courage"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "decency"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  *fort*  now known as Fort McHenry was  built prior to the War of 1812 to guard Baltimore harbor. ",
        "answers": [
            "mansion",
            " garrison",
            "tower",
            "museum"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " garrison"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Recent border  *confrontations*  between the two military groups lend  credence to the rumors of an impending war. ",
        "answers": [
            " enterprises",
            "consequences",
            " conferences",
            "disputes"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "disputes"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  cheetah is  *considered*  the fastest of all land animal. ",
        "answers": [
            "recorded  as",
            "substituted for",
            "compelled to be",
            "expected to  be"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "expected to  be"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Many apartments have  doors with a security window so that one may  *take a look*  outside  and observe visitors without being seen. ",
        "answers": [
            "block",
            " joke",
            "peek",
            "shake"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "peek"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In the play \"The Devil and  Daniel Webster\", the  *retorts*  attributed to Webster may be more  fiction than history. ",
        "answers": [
            "replies",
            "advice",
            "behavior",
            "possessions"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "replies"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Alaska boasts of several climates due to its   *lofty*  mountains. warm ocean currents, and frozen seas. ",
        "answers": [
            " towering",
            "countless",
            "rugged",
            "ageless"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " towering"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " *Adverse*  reviews in the New York press  may greatly change the prospects of a new Broadway production ",
        "answers": [
            " additional",
            "encouraging",
            " unfavorable",
            "subversive"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " unfavorable"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Prospects for an upturn in the economy remain  *bleak* . ",
        "answers": [
            "dismal",
            " indifferent",
            "encouraging",
            "unknown"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "dismal"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  pianist was  *adept*  at playing the arpeggios. ",
        "answers": [
            " proficient",
            "adjustable",
            "awkward",
            " careful"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " proficient"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Scientists believe that a 400-mile wide meteoric   *crater*  to the east of Hudson Bay may be the world's largest.  ",
        "answers": [
            " container",
            "depression",
            "locale",
            "mound"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "depression"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The company has decided to  offer  *incentives*  in the hope of increasing productivity. ",
        "answers": [
            "inducements",
            " training",
            "promotions",
            "bonuses"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "inducements"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The fer-de-lance, a kind of viper, is one of the most   *poisonous*  snakes. ",
        "answers": [
            "deadly",
            "vicious",
            "bad  tasting",
            "unhealthy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "deadly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "John  was not promoted because his work did not meet the manager's   *expectations* . ",
        "answers": [
            "anticipations",
            " expenditures",
            "expertise",
            "gaudiness"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "anticipations"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Part of the county area was  *annexed*  to the city in recent months.  ",
        "answers": [
            " joined",
            "separated",
            "dispensed",
            "revoked"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " joined"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "An  *immature*  teenager may start smoking in  order to appear older. ",
        "answers": [
            "shy",
            "juvenile",
            "naive",
            "insecure"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "juvenile"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The superintendent was the   *principal*  speaker at the school board meeting. ",
        "answers": [
            " only",
            "main",
            "outstanding",
            "strongest"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "main"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Volcanoes are formed  where the plates in the earth's crust  *meet* . ",
        "answers": [
            " crack",
            "intersect",
            "collapse",
            "float"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "collapse"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The use  of Navajo code-talkers resolved a situation of the utmost  *gravity*   in World War II. ",
        "answers": [
            "delicacy",
            "seriousness",
            "levity",
            " deadliness"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "seriousness"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Victoria Holtand William Shakespeare are  *prolific*  writers. ",
        "answers": [
            " productive",
            "famous",
            "esteemed",
            " celebrated"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " productive"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  director's  *spacious*  new office overlooked the city. ",
        "answers": [
            " quiet",
            "colorful",
            "roomy",
            "comfortable"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "roomy"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The   *founder*  of the American Red Cross was Clara Barton. ",
        "answers": [
            " leader",
            "backer",
            "discoverer",
            "originator"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "originator"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "That a driver   *swerves*  in order to avoid an accident can be proven by examining  the marks on the pavement. ",
        "answers": [
            "turns sharply",
            "stops quickly",
            "hits something  else",
            "goes backwards"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "turns sharply"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The company possesses  *unique*  research  capabilities. ",
        "answers": [
            "single",
            "only",
            "unequalled",
            " different"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "unequalled"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Lyndon  Johnson  *succeeded*  John Kennedy as president of the United States.  ",
        "answers": [
            " overruled",
            "preceded",
            "followed",
            "assisted"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "followed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  *lingering*  disease gradually broke down  his will. ",
        "answers": [
            "fatal",
            "persisting",
            "annoying",
            " infectious"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "persisting"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Milk is   *purified*  by heating it at 60*C for thirty minutes. ",
        "answers": [
            "cleansed",
            " stored",
            "mixed",
            "packaged"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "cleansed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The student's  application was turned down because it was  *incorrectly*  filled out.  ",
        "answers": [
            " belatedly",
            "roughly",
            "absurdly",
            "erroneously"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "erroneously"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Studies of  climatology  *indicate*  that volcanic dust in the atmosphere may  contribute to the onset of ice ages. ",
        "answers": [
            " explain",
            "insinuate",
            "suggest",
            "prove"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "suggest"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "A  cut in the budget put 10 percent of the state employees' jobs in   *jeopardy* . ",
        "answers": [
            "range",
            "review",
            " perspective",
            "danger"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "danger"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Carbon monoxide   *prevents*  hemoglobin from supplying oxygen to the body. ",
        "answers": [
            " discourages",
            "distracts",
            "impedes",
            " excuses"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "impedes"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "During  the American colonial period, the capable leaders  *instilled*  a  spirit of nationalism in the colonists. ",
        "answers": [
            " insatiated",
            "extirpated",
            "implanted",
            " extracted"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "implanted"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The guests at the luau enjoyed it  very much but refused to eat the  *raw*  fish. ",
        "answers": [
            " marinated",
            "fresh",
            "rotten",
            "uncooked"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "uncooked"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Bread has been a   *staple*  of the human diet since prehistoric times. ",
        "answers": [
            "great  delicacy",
            "basic part",
            "fastener",
            "highlight"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "basic part"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The  doctor asked the patient to  *disrobe*  before the examination. ",
        "answers": [
            "take  medicine",
            "breathe deeply",
            "relax",
            "undress"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "undress"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "We were told to   *intermingle*  with the guests. ",
        "answers": [
            "talk",
            " sing",
            "mix",
            "intercede"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "mix"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " When heated to temperatures above 1250 degrees Centigrade, clay   *fuses*  and becomes pottery or stoneware. ",
        "answers": [
            "burns  off",
            "steams up",
            "melts together",
            "decays"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "melts together"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The last week of classes is always  *very  busy*  because students are taking examinations, making applications to  the University, and extending their visas. ",
        "answers": [
            "hectic",
            " prolific",
            "fanatic",
            "eccentric"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "hectic"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Elizabeth Blackwell founded  *an academy*  to train women physicians  in 1868. ",
        "answers": [
            "a philosophy",
            "a clinic",
            "a school",
            "a company"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a school"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Martin Luther King   *detested*  injustice. ",
        "answers": [
            "recognized",
            "confronted",
            "suffered",
            " abhorred"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " abhorred"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The landscape can change   *abruptly*  after a rainstorm in the desert Southwest. ",
        "answers": [
            "quickly",
            " sharply",
            "favorably",
            "slightly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "quickly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The spectacle being  planned for the next Fourth of July party is quite  *awesome* . ",
        "answers": [
            "funny",
            " ordinary",
            "alarming",
            "prodigious"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "prodigious"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Ralph Nader always  *speaks out*  about everything. ",
        "answers": [
            "declares his  opinion",
            "agrees",
            "quarrels",
            "has an  interest"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "declares his  opinion"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Fear of pirate   *raids*  caused the Spaniards to fortify their coastline. ",
        "answers": [
            " invasions",
            "ships",
            "arms",
            "investigations"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " invasions"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The conditions under which visas are given are quite   *explicit* , so nobody should complain if they are not given one.  ",
        "answers": [
            " equivocal",
            "dubious",
            "strict",
            "clear"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "clear"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "John  didn't enjoy the rock concert because he thought the  *tempo*  was  bad. ",
        "answers": [
            "audience",
            "rhythm",
            "singer",
            " weather"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "rhythm"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Allowing fields to lie  *fallow*   is one means of restoring fertility. ",
        "answers": [
            " unplanted",
            "plowed",
            "watered",
            "seeded"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " unplanted"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When  students do not have time to read a novel before class, they read  *an  outline of the plot*  instead. ",
        "answers": [
            "an article",
            "a  synopsis",
            "a critique",
            "an essay"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a  synopsis"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "J.P.Morgan had a reputation for being a   *prudent*  businessman. ",
        "answers": [
            "clever",
            "wealthy",
            " careful",
            "dishonest"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "dishonest"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Written divorce  *regulations*  first appeared in the legal code of  ancient Babylonia. ",
        "answers": [
            "rules",
            "outlines",
            " regularities",
            "specifics"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "rules"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In the fall the weather is  *cool*  in the  morning but warm by midday. ",
        "answers": [
            "chilly",
            "rusty",
            "silly",
            "fluffy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "chilly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Of  the approximately 400 billion  *packages*  used yearly in the United  States, half are for food and drink. ",
        "answers": [
            " posters",
            "suitcases",
            "dishes",
            "containers"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "containers"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "It will be  necessary for the doctor to  *widen*  the pupils of your eyes with  some drops in order to examine them. ",
        "answers": [
            " massage",
            "treat",
            "dilate",
            "soothe"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "dilate"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The real meaning of the  poem was  *obscured*  by the pretentious language in which it was  written. ",
        "answers": [
            "exposed",
            "apparent",
            "hidden",
            "shown"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "hidden"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " According to a belief  *prevalent*  in many places, a small, forked  stick referred to as a \"divining rod\" is able to locate subterranean springs.  ",
        "answers": [
            "held  sacred",
            "broadly accepted",
            "documented",
            "detected"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "broadly accepted"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Heterogeneous catalysts are  *widely*  used in  petroleum production. ",
        "answers": [
            "strongly",
            "extensively",
            "weightily",
            " narrowly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "extensively"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Because Dolly is such a good cook, she has  *concocted*  a great new  recipe. ",
        "answers": [
            "created",
            "named",
            "epitomized",
            " baked"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "created"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "  *Given*  current economic trends, liberal increases in the money  supply appear unlikely in the extreme. ",
        "answers": [
            " Following",
            "Presenting",
            "In view of",
            "In lieu of"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "In view of"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In a   *search*  to further his knowledge of the unknown, man has explored  the earth, the sea, and now, outer space. ",
        "answers": [
            "quest",
            " colloquy",
            "fantasy",
            "documentary"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "quest"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " Parsley is  *cultivated*  throughout much of the world. ",
        "answers": [
            "seen",
            " grown",
            "dried",
            "cooked"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " grown"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Third World countries have  had enough of the industrialised nations'  *exploitation*  of their  natural resources. ",
        "answers": [
            "trading",
            "purchasing",
            "misuse",
            " desire"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "misuse"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "As a result of severe  illness or treatments for illness one may become temporarily   *hairless* . ",
        "answers": [
            "bald",
            "hoarse",
            "lame",
            "stiff"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "bald"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Valium is  a strong drug that can cause a driver to  *sleep*  at the wheel.  ",
        "answers": [
            " dream",
            "sneeze",
            "doze",
            "snore"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "doze"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Ralph Bunche won a Nobel Prize  in 1950 for his peacemaking  *efforts*  as a United Nations diplomat.  ",
        "answers": [
            " requests",
            "attempts",
            "offers",
            "trips"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "attempts"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Even as a  child Thomas Edison had a very  *inquisitive*  mind; at the age of  three he performed his first experiment. ",
        "answers": [
            "complex",
            " brilliant",
            "mature",
            "curious"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "curious"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In an annulment, a marriage is declared   *invalid* . ",
        "answers": [
            "ill",
            "unhappy",
            "unfinished",
            " void"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " void"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " In order to assure that no infection will occur, a surgeon must   *wash*  his hands and arms with an antiseptic soap prior to  operating. ",
        "answers": [
            "scrub",
            "crib",
            "club",
            "grab"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "scrub"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "You must  *have lost your marbles*  if you're seriously considering buying that house",
        "answers": [
            "be serious",
            "be crazy",
            "be adventurous",
            "be happy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "be crazy"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "If you don't mind me saying so I think  *you're a bit over the top* , aren't you?",
        "answers": [
            "you're exaggerating a bit",
            "you're joking a little",
            "you're laughing a bit",
            "you're describing a little"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "you're exaggerating a bit"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "All right then if you like  *I'll put my cards on the table* .",
        "answers": [
            "I'll tell you a story",
            "I'll tell you what to do",
            "I'll tell you something",
            "I'll tell you my honest opinion"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "I'll tell you my honest opinion"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I'd appreciate that. Go on,  *I'm all ears* ..",
        "answers": [
            "I can hear what you're saying",
            "I am listening very carefully",
            "I am listening to you",
            "I can't hear a word"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "I am listening very carefully"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Well in the first place all the windows are broken, which is  *a real pain in the neck* ",
        "answers": [
            "a bad ache",
            "a serious ache",
            "a serious problem",
            "a bad shock"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a serious problem"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Nobody knows what's  *going on* ?",
        "answers": [
            "meaning",
            "continuing",
            "happening",
            "taking"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "happening"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Don't worry we'll  *see you're all right* .",
        "answers": [
            "look at you",
            "look on you",
            "look for you",
            "look after you"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "look after you"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "What you need is something that will  *pick you up* .",
        "answers": [
            "make you feel better",
            "make you stand better",
            "make you hold on better",
            "make you stay on better"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "make you feel better"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I simply  *can't stand*  sugar in my tea or coffee.",
        "answers": [
            "can't eat",
            "can't drink",
            "can't tolerate",
            "can't allow"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "can't tolerate"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I have a feeling that she's  *taking you for a ride* .",
        "answers": [
            "taking you in a car",
            "pulling you along",
            "trying to trick you",
            "trying to push you"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "trying to trick you"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "They tried  *in vain* to save enough money to buy a house and so finally they rented one.",
        "answers": [
            "without money",
            "without trial",
            "without success",
            "without work"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "without success"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Although Romeo and Juliet  *were deeply in love* ,they still managed to kill themselves.",
        "answers": [
            "loved each other often",
            "loved each other very much",
            "loved each other most of the time",
            "loved each other mostly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "loved each other often"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I cannot understand why she did that, it really  *doesn't add up* .",
        "answers": [
            "doesn't calculate",
            "isn't mathematics",
            "doesn't make sense",
            "makes the wrong addition"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "doesn't make sense"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "All the students got high marks in the test but Mary  *stood out* .",
        "answers": [
            "got a lot of marks",
            "got higher marks than someone",
            "got very good marks",
            "got the most marks of all"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "got the most marks of all"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "He has sold his house and has no job and so now  *he has next to nothing* ",
        "answers": [
            "he is unemployed",
            "he has almost no money",
            "he has a few things",
            "he has nothing at all"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "he has almost no money"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "As a newspaper reporter she always wanted to get information  *at first hand* .",
        "answers": [
            "quickly",
            "slowly",
            "easily",
            "directly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "directly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I think we can safely say now that we have got our money back, we are  *home and dry* ",
        "answers": [
            "have not got wet",
            "have got no water",
            "have been successful",
            "have got home dry"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "have been successful"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I'm sure that he could make a better job of being prime minister *any day of the week* .",
        "answers": [
            "whatever the details",
            "whatever the time",
            "whatever the circumstances",
            "whatever the week"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "whatever the circumstances"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Don't worry we pride ourselves on being helpful to all our customers and getting that booked for you is  *all in a day's work*  for us",
        "answers": [
            "perfectly easy",
            "perfectly simple",
            "perfectly done",
            "perfectly normal"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "perfectly normal"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Yes, we went away on holiday last week but it rained  *day in, day out* ",
        "answers": [
            "every single day",
            "every other day",
            "every second day",
            "every two days"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "every single day"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I think the time has now come when we'll simply have to  *call it a day* ",
        "answers": [
            "stop trying",
            "stop thinking",
            "stop working",
            "stop going"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "stop working"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "You know what they said about radio that it had  *had its day*  but it's still going strong",
        "answers": [
            "stopped being clever",
            "stopped being popular",
            "stopped being heard",
            "stopped being good"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "stopped being popular"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "If you think I'm going to parachute out of a plane for fun, you must be  *out of your mind* .",
        "answers": [
            "mad",
            "unsure",
            "unusual",
            "uncertain"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "unsure"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Wait till they're  *out of sight* ,and then I'll show you what I'm buying them for Christmas.",
        "answers": [
            "unable to show",
            "unable to find",
            "unable to follow",
            "unable to see"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "unable to show"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I'm very sorry but you're  *out of luck* because we sold the last one about twenty minutes ago.",
        "answers": [
            "unhappy",
            "unlucky",
            "unable",
            "undecided"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "undecided"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Wait until they're  *out of earshot* , then I tell you exactly what happened to them when they were on holiday.",
        "answers": [
            "unable to tell",
            "unable to hear",
            "unable to say",
            "unable to speak"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "unable to hear"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "You have a limited number of minutes to answer the test and you've spent 3 minutes so  *you're out of time* .",
        "answers": [
            "you've used up your time",
            "you've used in your time",
            "you've used for your time",
            "you've used out your time"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "you've used in your time"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "As usual he left it to the last moment and as a consequence he *missed the boat* ",
        "answers": [
            "didn't take advantage of the situation",
            "didn't take advantage of the opportunity",
            "didn't take advantage of the fare",
            "didn't take advantage of the date"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "didn't take advantage of the opportunity"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I'm sorry to tell you that  *you've burnt your boats*  now and so you won't be able to go back.",
        "answers": [
            "your current situation cannot be reversed",
            "your current situation cannot be repeated",
            "your current situation cannot be retaken",
            "your current situation cannot be restyled"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "your current situation cannot be reversed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I told her I understood exactly what she was feeling as we were both after all  *in the same boat* .",
        "answers": [
            "in a similar case",
            "in a similar find",
            "in a similar take",
            "in a similar situation"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "in a similar situation"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "No matter how smoothly things are running, you can always rely on Charlie to  *rock the boat* .",
        "answers": [
            "spoil something",
            "spoil anything",
            "spoil everything",
            "spoil nothing"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "spoil everything"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Although they were a couple well into their 80's everything in their house was always  *shipshape* .",
        "answers": [
            "very old",
            "very neat",
            "very fresh",
            "very clean"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "very neat"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I'm sorry I didn't  *take in*  what he said",
        "answers": [
            "listen",
            "hear",
            "understand",
            "note"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "understand"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I hope she  *gets through*  her exams next week.",
        "answers": [
            "passes",
            "follows",
            "takes",
            "stands"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "passes"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "What time do you  *get up*  in the morning?",
        "answers": [
            "leave home",
            "start for work",
            "finish off sleep",
            "get out of bed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "get out of bed"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When you stop work, you can  *take up*  golf.",
        "answers": [
            "finish playing",
            "start playing",
            "stop playing",
            "enjoy playing"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "start playing"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Don't  *overdo it*  because you're very tired",
        "answers": [
            "do a lot",
            "do a little",
            "do too little",
            "do too much"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "do too much"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The audience  *held their breath*  as the magician started to saw a woman half.",
        "answers": [
            "watched anxiously",
            "stopped breathing",
            "couldn't breathe",
            "couldn't watch"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "watched anxiously"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The police officer called out to the driver to  *hold on*  until he arrived",
        "answers": [
            "continue",
            "listen",
            "wait",
            "attend"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "wait"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In the end she lost her temper and told her daughter to  *hold her tongue* ",
        "answers": [
            "stand still",
            "speak up",
            "start speaking",
            "be quiet"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "be quiet"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "There's no need to change any of the regulations this year as the old ones will still  *hold good*  this year, too.",
        "answers": [
            "be finished",
            "be all right",
            "be necessary",
            "be careful"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "be all right"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I don't know what it is exactly but she seems to have some kind of  *hold over*  him",
        "answers": [
            "control over",
            "look over",
            "trust over",
            "belief over"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "control over"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "We need to do something about it! This situation is getting  *out of hand* !",
        "answers": [
            "too big",
            "too organized",
            "out of control",
            "out of order"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "out of control"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Now the grandparents have the children  *on their hands* .",
        "answers": [
            "in their care",
            "in trouble",
            "spanked",
            "to obey them"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "in their care"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "This last year, my company has made money  *hand over fist* !",
        "answers": [
            "with a lot of struggle",
            "at a huge rate",
            "poorly",
            "distribution"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "at a huge rate"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "As soon as he  *laid his hands on*  all that money, he donated part of it to charitable institutions.",
        "answers": [
            "stole",
            "scattered",
            "released",
            "took possession of"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "took possession of"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The beginning of a new generation of computer software is  *at hand* ",
        "answers": [
            "imminent",
            "remote",
            "current",
            "in someone's possession"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "imminent"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I just want to stay at home and watch television and  *take it easy* .",
        "answers": [
            "sleep",
            "",
            " down",
            "eat"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": " down"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "relax",
        "answers": [
            " *Am I allowed to*  smoke in here?",
            "May I",
            "Must I",
            "Can I"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "May I"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Will I",
        "answers": [
            " *Are you any good at cooking* ?",
            "Can you cook sometimes",
            "Do you cook very often",
            "Can you cook well"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "Can you cook well"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Do you like cooking",
        "answers": [
            "When do you  *do the washing up* ?",
            "clean the dishes",
            "do the housework",
            "wash the floor"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "clean the dishes"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "clean the windows",
        "answers": [
            "She never  *shouts at*  her children.",
            "makes conversation with",
            "calls out to",
            "talks in a loud voice to"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "talks in a loud voice to"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I  *can't wait*  to hear about your English class.",
        "answers": [
            "am eager to",
            "am late to",
            "am indifferent",
            "am happy to"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "am happy to"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I am glad I was able  *to be there for*  my friend when her mom died.",
        "answers": [
            "to cry with",
            "to offer support in time of need for",
            "to visit",
            "to travel with"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "to cry with"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "You've got me  *head over heels* !",
        "answers": [
            "angry at you",
            "impatient",
            "in love with you",
            "disappointed"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "impatient"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I love you  *bunches* !",
        "answers": [
            "a little",
            "a lot",
            "too much",
            "less than before"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "too much"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I wish I could trust you again, but all that you ever did to me was  *to let me down* .",
        "answers": [
            "to make me cry",
            "to make me angry",
            "to despise me",
            "to disappoint me"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "to make me angry"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "They're very generous in that museum ? not only is the entrance fee reasonable but they give you a brochure *for free* .",
        "answers": [
            "at no cost",
            "at little cost",
            "at some cost",
            "at low cost"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "at little cost"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "That's the thing about Charlie even when things are really bad he doesn't panic and  *keeps his cool* .",
        "answers": [
            "stays calm",
            "turns on the air conditioning",
            "uses a fan",
            "puts ice on his head"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "uses a fan"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "In a situation like his of course the one thing you must do is *keep the wolf from the door*  and try to find money to pay all the bills.",
        "answers": [
            "get rid of wild animals",
            "get enough money to live on",
            "make sure the door is locked",
            "not let wild animals in"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "get rid of wild animals"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "At least Charlie can manage that but he doesn't go telling everyone about his problem and  *keeps himself to himself* .",
        "answers": [
            "talks to himself a lot",
            "doesn't go out much",
            "stays in a lot",
            "doesn't talk about himself to others"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "doesn't go out much"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Some of his friends are a bit worried about him because he doesn't seem so friendly to them as he used to be and  *keeps his distance* .",
        "answers": [
            "doesn't let people get too close",
            "doesn't travel far",
            "decides how far to go",
            "doesn't like travelling"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "doesn't like travelling"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The main thing that you have to admire him for is that he doesn't get into trouble and  *keeps his nose clean* .",
        "answers": [
            "blows his nose a lot",
            "behaves legally",
            "sneezes often",
            "breathes easily"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "blows his nose a lot"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I'm sorry that looks awful ? those two colours  *don't go together* .",
        "answers": [
            "smash",
            "crash",
            "clash",
            "hash"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "clash"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "After what you've  *gone through* , I'm sure you need a holiday",
        "answers": [
            "felt",
            "sensed",
            "acted",
            "experienced"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "experienced"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "We won't  *go into*  that now but I don't think we can avoid the subject much longer",
        "answers": [
            "discuss",
            "enter",
            "introduce",
            "interrupt"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "discuss"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": " *He's gone right down in my estimation*  now that I've heard what he has done to his family.",
        "answers": [
            "I think often of him",
            "I think a lot of him",
            "I don't think at all of him",
            "I don't think much of him"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "I don't think at all of him"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "My advice to you is to make your mind up before it's too late and simply  *go for it* .",
        "answers": [
            "take the opportunity soon",
            "take the opportunity fairly",
            "take the opportunity now",
            "take the opportunity slowly"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "take the opportunity now"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "You shouldn't worry about the exam because you have prepared well and you'll probably find it  *a piece of cake* .",
        "answers": [
            "easy to digest",
            "easy to read",
            "easy to start",
            "very easy"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "very easy"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The trouble with you is that you are a bit selfish and your sole philosophy is to  *have your cake and eat it* .",
        "answers": [
            "expect too much of life",
            "lead a life of pleasure",
            "spend your life eating",
            "eat too much"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "expect too much of life"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "When he heard that the necklace had been stolen,  *he dropped it like a hot potato* ",
        "answers": [
            "he let it fall from his hands",
            "he suddenly lost interest in it",
            "he gave it to somebody else",
            "he hid it in the fridge"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "he suddenly lost interest in it"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "He sits and watches TV all day and has turned into  *a veritable couch potato* .",
        "answers": [
            "a good sleeper",
            "an enthusiast",
            "a very lazy person",
            "a deep thinker"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "a very lazy person"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "Thanks to you we're really  *in the soup*  now and I don't honestly know why I ever listen to you.",
        "answers": [
            "in an interesting situation",
            "in deep trouble",
            "in an unusual situation",
            "in rough water"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "in deep trouble"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "He's  *up to his ears in*  work and cannot possibly see you now",
        "answers": [
            "fully occupied with",
            "very interested in",
            "not involved with",
            "concerned with"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "fully occupied with"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "If you  *give me a hand* , then I shall be able to finish more quickly.",
        "answers": [
            "take my hand",
            "help me",
            "take my fingers",
            "pick me up"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "help me"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "I prefer to talk to people  *face to face*  rather than to talk on the phone.",
        "answers": [
            "in person",
            "facing them",
            "looking at them",
            "seeing them"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "in person"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "The manager dismissed the new proposal  *out of hand*  and said that it was not at all practical.",
        "answers": [
            "quickly",
            "utterly",
            "directly",
            "simply"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "utterly"
    },
    {
        "content": "",
        "question": "As she is new to the job I would ask you  *to keep an eye on*  her for the time being",
        "answers": [
            "look at",
            "consider",
            "check",
            "observe"
        ],
        "rightAnswer": "observe"
    }
]